Publisher ID	Publisher Details
0736	"This is sample text data for New Moon Books, publisher 0736 in the pubs database. New Moon Books is located in Boston, Massachusetts."
0877	"This is sample text data for Binnet & Hardley, publisher 0877 in the pubs database. Binnet & Hardley is located in Washington, D.C."
1389	"This is sample text data for Algodata Infosystems, publisher 1389 in the pubs database. Algodata Infosystems is located in Berkeley, California."
1622	"This is sample text data for Five Lakes Publishing, publisher 1622 in the pubs database. Five Lakes Publishing is located in Chicago, Illinois."
1756	"This is sample text data for Ramona Publishers, publisher 1756 in the pubs database. Ramona Publishers is located in Dallas, Texas."
9901	"This is sample text data for GGG&G, publisher 9901 in the pubs database. GGG&G is located in M?nchen, Germany."
9952	"This is sample text data for Scootney Books, publisher 9952 in the pubs database. Scootney Books is located in New York City, New York."
9999	"This is sample text data for Lucerne Publishing, publisher 9999 in the pubs database. Lucerne publishing is located in Paris, France."
